Okay, Ben.
2 "Ben Jaques-Leslie (MMB)" (1727942400)
Hey Jonathan. How's it going.
3 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
And good. Are you ready to go or should I lock?
4 "Ben Jaques-Leslie (MMB)" (1727942400)
What the Does it, do we start start at nine or do we start start at.
5 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
So start start at nine oh one.
6 "Ben Jaques-Leslie (MMB)" (1727942400)
Probably? Nine oh one. Okay, I need to get myself set up a little bit more. Is that's ok?
7 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
And I'm gonna see if I can lock people out.
8 "Ben Jaques-Leslie (MMB)" (1727942400)
Okay, Hey Jonathan.
9 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
Then.
10 "Ben Jaques-Leslie (MMB)" (1727942400)
Do you see in the lobby like a room being asked to join? Might be called Cedar.
11 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
Yeah, that's the room I.
12 "Ben Jaques-Leslie (MMB)" (1727942400)
And do you think you could. Thanks. Okay, can you hear, can you hear, can you hear?
13 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
Well, I can but with an echo now.
14 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Okay.
15 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Okay. Can you hear me.
16 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
Hi Eileen, we're, just getting set up. I do have meeting locked.
17 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Hey, Jonathan, can you hear me?
18 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
I can. That's a little bit better. Okay.
19 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Should be coming through the video, the screen like what I'm pointing at right now.
20 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Do you think you could, bring that back up maybe? It looks like I can't see it. Oh, oh, NO never mind. That's fine. Just seeing myself tell my shoes. That's great.
21 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Okay, I'm gonna turn off this camera and let me get my stuff set. I was getting nervous.
22 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
Yeah, you probably should.
23 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
I think we do better work when we're a little bit nervous. I should be nervous.
24 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
But yeah, but you're gonna be fine. We've done this before.
25 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
How many people am I expecting?
26 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
You know I did never look. I'm not sure. I see.
27 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
I mean if it's just us then I shouldn't be nervous, right?
28 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Right? Well, I think part.
29 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
Part of it is they record it, so, even if people go to other breakout sessions, you know, they.
30 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
It didn't just look at me forever.
31 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
They can watch this later too.
32 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
So steady in reassuring. Thanks. Thanks, Jonathan.
33 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
I think you might need to go to your presenter support training more.
34 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
We met!
35 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
You and E.
36 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
No.
37 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
Silene and I did zip up. Quarter zip.
38 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Thank you. It is awesome. I'm learning a lot, but I'm hoping that, I'm hoping I'm still able to be connected to DCWF because the people that we're serving are, you know, below the poverty line in most cases and so our enrolled in programs or need programs and services I think especially senior things, so.
39 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Like there's a lot to learn.
40 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
I forget where was it you were working? Was it.
41 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Habitat for Yeah Habitat for humanity. That's awesome.
42 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Yeah. Alright, what am I gotta close this sharing there's.
43 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
My dog has just settled down for a long nap. Oh I'm sorry. Did I disturb your rest?
44 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
You're ready Eileen, you've got your script and everything. Okay.
45 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Yeah, I was thinking, starting at nine oh five seemed to work really well yesterday, just letting people have enough time to come in. So I thought when we unlocked the, meeting or just the greeting and then say and put in the chat we'll just get started at nine oh five to.
46 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Allow everyone to come in because not everyone's there right of the dot.
47 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
Well, and it's the 1st breakout session, so if they're not familiar, this would be the one that they are, learning on, I agree.
48 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Okay, can you see my screen ok?
49 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
We do, yeah.
50 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Oh NO. Oops. It's got my little plugin for my mouse.
51 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Yeah Jonathan, did you overlap with Cody Tuddle at DHS?
52 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
No, I don't know that name. Yeah.
53 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
He works here now.
54 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
I was chit chatting with him.
55 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
Is he a white guy? Yes yes. I wonder, yeah, I, they, I think I've heard of him.
56 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
He's the thing of legends. I even hey I updated this presentation with like newer research and everything so that we are not using ten year old research now. Feel pretty I I don't get to say something like a relatively new field cause now it's like a very old.
57 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
It's likes.
58 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
I'm always impressed with, what the researchers do and actually we had Deb Schlick a couple years ago was our keynote and I did something on scarcity and deep poverty. That was good. Were you guys able to see Troyer yesterday?
59 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Oh NO. Where was he?
60 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
He was our keynote yesterday.
61 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
You know, I didn't get any. Should I have registered for the whole conference?
62 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
You know, Ben I'm gonna send you If you didn't then you didn't get the links, but you don't have to register to attend any, any, session that you want. So I'm just gonna send those links and you can just look at them and see if there's anything else that you'd like to attend.
63 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Cool. Thanks.
64 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
So shall we let people in?
65 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Sure.
66 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
I guess. Do what do you think? Yeah. Well, we could wait right now.
67 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Until nine because if we're not actually starting until nine oh five, that'd be like a long time.
68 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Like just like yeah. Okay.
69 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Anticipation will only build.
70 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Yeah. I didn't bring any flames or anything. Yeah.
71 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Yeah, but I think this is gonna be a really exciting time for, for data work with all of the changes to Mfip with the sanctioned policies and the six month reporting just to see how much of a difference that makes and from a former employment counselor perspective, what I would really be interested in most is engagement and if engagement is gonna drop off with less.
72 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Compliance, fewer compliance tools and, you know, thinking, well, I don't have to communicate with my financial worker, but every six months, you know, the ECs will be like, NO NO NO, but I still want to talk to you monthly, weekly cause I have all these like great tools to help you navigate through the program. So I'm gonna be really curious about that.
73 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Yeah.
74 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
Yeah, you're right, and also how it affects the self support index, yeah.
75 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Self support index should just adjust because it's a state level change but hey Eileen, I probably gonna have a hard time seeing the chat because it's in the web browser. Are you gonna be able I mean, I can go to it, but it's gonna end up being like this for me to see it.
76 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Yeah, so we'll monitor the chat. Do you want me just to encourage people to use the hand raise function if they have something or do you want to just say if you have a question, just park it in the chat and we'll, we'll take a look at it at the end of the presentation.
77 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
There's gonna be a lot of times that I pause for like trying to get feedback from the group. So I'm gonna ask you to keep an eye on it, and if there's a like and try to assess it because otherwise like it will look really bad if I'm here and I guess I can bring up the let me see if I can just bring up the, where is the chat?
78 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
This is why I'm gonna be on mute. This is why I'm in here.
79 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Okay, so if you could just help me keep an eye on the chat cause I don't think I'm gonna be able to see it very well. And I'm gonna put stuff into the chat from time to time.
80 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Yeah, and hopefully we will have some, you know, people who want to say something in the pause. We have a lot of, I think, shyer people who, you know, wouldn't come off mute. I'm not one of those people.
81 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Okay, so if, yeah, I had just planned on using the chat, but actually if you think if we because I wasn't sure if we would allow people to come off of mute, but if that's fine, then I'm happy to Yeah we'll just say you know.
82 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Raise your hand and put, you know, there's a combination of things that we can.
83 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And we go until what time?
84 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
I think this is until 1020. Okay. Yep, and then the breakout session two is 1040, so yeah. Okay.
85 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
Alright, well we've got 77 in the lobby. I'm gonna let them in and turn it over to you guys.
86 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Sounds good. Thanks, Jonathan.
87 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
Good luck. Thanks.
88 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Good luck.
89 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Break a leg. Thanks.
90 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Are you gonna say anything Eileen? The welcome.
91 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Yeah yep ok everyone, good morning. We are so happy you're here for the 1st breakout session. We're gonna give people a few minutes to get in and we're gonna start the presentation right at nine oh five. So there's a last cup of coffee or anything you want to grab, you have a little bit of time.
92 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Yeah, and we do have the chat function open, so if while you're waiting you maybe wanted to put in like why you chose this particular session, that would be really interesting to know.
93 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
2 min.
94 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Two more minutes I think we have mostly everyone who registered. We'll just see if there's anyone else who wants to get in here.
95 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
And it looks like you're at a university.
96 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Me? Yeah. Why?
97 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
It looks like you're in like a lecture room.
98 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Oh, well we do have a board, so that's good. Yeah, where I'm at Centaniel, the Centaniel office building right now. Sentenial is you're at the mall and you're looking at the capital to the right.
99 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Okay, neat. Yeah oh good morning, everyone. I see some familiar names from yesterday in the chat, people are saying good morning in the chat.
100 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
I thought so. Hi. I just dropped a link to the slides if you want them. One cool thing is you can save them as a PDF using those little boards and little bars. And, so.
101 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Yeah, I think that's great especially with data because there are a lot of numbers. It's good to be able to have a chance to look back. Yeah.
102 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Well, I don't alright go ahead.
103 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
All right, everyone, good morning. Welcome to the 1st breakout session. It is nine oh five, so we're gonna get started. Just some housekeeping. Everyone is on mute. If you have a question, you can put it in the chat, you can raise your hand, and Ben.
104 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
I'll pause at certain moments in his presentation to get some feedback, so, you know, we'd love any comments that you have. The topic is how scarcity affects you and your clients, and I'm just gonna give you a little bit of background on Ben. Ben Jakes Leslie is the results coordinator in the budget and results division at Minnesota Management and budget specializing in performance measurements.
105 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
And program evaluation for state government initiatives. He brings over a decade of experience in data analysis and evaluation research across federal, state and international contexts, including causal analysis studies on federal workforce policies, predictive modeling for social programs and.
106 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Leading data infrastructure projects supporting millions and public assistance programs. Ben holds a masters in international Affairs from UC San Diego focused on international development and a bachelors and mathematics from UNC Japa Hill. I have heard Ben speak before and you guys are in for treat. I'll turn it over to Ben.
107 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Wow. Thanks Eileen. I can't see any of you. I just see my slides, but I'm really excited to be here and to be chatting with you. I like, thanks for the introduction. I guess I don't really have to say anything else but I will dive in in a se.
108 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Seconds, let me just get my set up. Okay I think I know what I'm doing. Okay, so i've done this presentation for about ten years now, which is like utterly shocking thing for me to say. And so I actually had to do a complete like a revision of this with new information. Luckily, I can say if you saw me present this.
109 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Ten years ago, the lessons are still basically the same. Shockingly. Our brains have not changed completely over the past ten years. So anyway, thank you very much for all, all for being here. Oh, one note, I cannot see the chat very well, and I cannot see hands being raised very well because of my computer, so I'm asking.
110 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
I lean to try to be my interpreter and my conduit for information from there, but alright, so we will get going. Alright, oops. Okay, so 1st of all, I just want you to start with three people and think about what their day might be like. So.
111 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
1st of all, I want you to try to think about, and I imagine this might be an easy thing for some of you to think about, but a financial worker, who is beginning of the month, beginning of some period, and there's lots of folks at the door who need assistance.
112 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Now think about a mom or parent with a low income in Minnesota who's got bills to pay. And lastly, think about somebody who's a chronically insecure man or person.
113 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Doesn't know when their next meal will come. I don't want you to answer or tell me what you're what you think they have in common right now. I just want you to like hold on to it in your brain while we move on for me to give you a preview.
114 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Of the plan for the session. So just keep them in mind. So we're gonna start with thinking about scarcity and describing what we mean when I talk about scarcity.
115 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
That feeling of scarcity actually produces sort of similar effects in our brains across all kinds of different scarcity. And the 1st thing that tends to happen is something called.
116 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
It strains our bandwidth, and we'll go into detail about that. And when people's bandwidth is strained, they start doing something called tunneling or they tunnel. So these are things that happen when folks are feeling scarcity.
117 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And scarcity, as we'll see, is something that can happen in a variety of different ways. But scarcity poverty is sort of a very specific type of feeling of scarcity and that we are gonna kind of dig into in a little bit more detail.
118 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
They have all these different things scarcity, bandwidth tunneling, thinking about poverty is scarcity, the kind of information or knowledge we have about these comes from now like a not very news field called behavioral science. So I'm gonna talk about a little bit about what behavioral science is and some lessons that we have.
119 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Have from behavioral science.
120 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And then we're gonna close with thinking about how we can design systems and our work with people for understanding and accepting the scarcity that we experience and that they experience. So I'm gonna try to cover a lot of stuff. Luckily we have quite a bit of time, but I mostly like doing this session for you.
121 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
You all to share and discuss what, where you feel like what we're talking about connects to your work and your, the folks that you work with. So I'm gonna do a couple of mentee polls where you can get out your phone and type in and we'll see some visualizations and I'd love to make good use of the chat.
122 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And also if you have something to say, certainly I think probably raise your hand and then come off mute and, and feel free to share. So I've built in, I don't know, four or five different times for us to share because that's generally what I find to be the most fun and useful part of doing these sessions because I've never had any of your jobs and you all have.
123 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Have your jobs probably know a lot more about all these things personally than I can.
124 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Alright, and feel free to ask questions throughout and I'm asked Eileen to to let me know. All right, so let's go back to the things that people have in common. So what does the financial worker, the mother, the food and secure person have in common?
125 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Anybody want to put in anything in the chat? I can't see them, so I'm gonna wait I'm gonna wait for a minute or two. I might have given it away. Oh my God, June. Actually, I can apparently I can see that I can see the chat, flash it through.
126 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Stress also true. Great Carol. I love also I can see your names. It's like name text. Oh yes, heather. I love that. It's very true. Yep. Great. Well, thank you all very much. Yes, I kind of gave it away in the beginning, with scarcity as kind of the main driver of what I've.
127 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Trying to get up, but all of these things I think are part of, part of scarcity. Well, yeah, they're all experiencing scarcity. They might have different sources of that scarcity, you know? So, you know, the financial worker.
128 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Has a scarcity of time to deal with all the people. The mom has scarcity of income and the the man has a scarcity of calories. These things are clearly very different. You can't each time and you can't, you know, well, you can spend time I suppose. But you can't.
129 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
At week time, but they're all very different things. But what is interesting is that when research researchers have explored these scarcity of these things, our brains tend to behave in simpler similar ways regardless of the source of the scarcity or what you're scarce in. And so this session is gonna be all, all about. So they're all very different, but it's similar behavior.
130 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Come out of these different, different types of scarcity. Alright, so I'm gonna switch to a mentee poll, so you can take your phones and scan this. And in fact I'm gonna go ahead and do it too.
131 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And what I like you to do is go ahead and enter maybe one, one or two words. There's different, different places you can enter it where you feel scared.
132 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Where you feel scarcity in your old, in your life. And I'm gonna switch over this. And here's the thing right there.
133 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Flooding in.
134 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
I love it. Oh, it's great. This is fun. I've never used like they've never used the word cloud before, but I'm gonna give a little bit more time for folks to to respond.
135 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Alright, so I see some, some things coming up very, very big, right? Time and money are huge and right in the center, and if we look kind of around the edges, we see things that are sort of similar, you know, like money to pay bills, free time, income.
136 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Resources, oh, there's some really interesting ones too. So health, that's a really, that's one I hadn't thought of, but that is I now I'm remembering that is something I've heard in other sessions.
137 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
That's such a good point, you know, I guess when I see rural area I think of like access maybe. Energy is a really good one. So clearly there's some things that are kind of coming out. Does anybody have any reflections on any of the.
138 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Any of these words that you're seeing, that you'd like to share with everybody?
139 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Thanks. Yeah, Scarcity of accesses I I, when I've, it's a real big change going around the state there, it's a very, as much as people might say it's not very heterogeneous state. It's a very different big place. Sorry, I missed the last comment. What it is.
140 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Right, big difference. Access to the things is very, could be a big constraint. It's great. Yeah, this time energy resources money is definitely very central.
141 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Alright, thank you very much for participating in that. Yeah, for sure. Yes, thank you Eileen.
142 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And if you have, if you wanna speak, you can. Okay, thank you very much. I think we have a lot in common as regards to scarcity as we can see. We all experienced.
143 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Is it in different ways. And again, what I think is so interesting is that you would think that like a scarcity of time and a scarcity of money would make you do really different things. I mean, they're really different. So it's kind of wild to me that in fact, when we experience these things, we actually start behaving in the same kind of way.
144 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
So, the 1st thing scarcity does is tax what researchers call bandwidth, which is the brain's underlying capacity to think, decide, and regulate behavior. There's a few different ways that I've liked to think about this, so like as.
145 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
As you can see I've got a traffic traffic lane closed here. So that's one way I like to think about it that like when you have, when you're on your commute and then, you know, a road is closed or, a lane is, you know, like an exit is maybe closed, you know.
146 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
The traffic has to change. Maybe all the traffic shifts into one lane. And this causes people to start making mistakes, right? The traffic slows down, maybe you take the wrong exit, maybe something happens in fact just the other day on 904a lane was closed.
147 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And it was quite sudden and the person in front of me, their break lights weren't working and they were at a complete stop, and I had to slam on my brakes. And it was very scary and I blamed great construction, and it taxed me, I made a mistake. Luckily it didn't end up that bad. But.
148 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
That's sort of an analogy for it. Another analogy might be like, I've seen some people's internet browsers where they like have so many tiny browsers open that they're like minuscule and you can't like actually see them. So when you do that, right, you're taxing the like the bandwidth of.
149 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
The internet you're on. And so each page you're trying to load, it's a little bit slower and a little bit not doesn't work as well. But I think the key point about all of these things is that you're not kind of less.
150 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Intelligent or less like I wasn't a worst driver, right, in that moment. I I wasn't, I wasn't motivated to not drive well, but my capacity, the capacity of the lane was like.
151 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Upset things and made there to be ability to make mistakes. Everybody's performance degraded. All the cars slowed down, all the websites slowed down. So when bandwidth is taxed, it makes everything more difficult and more likely.
152 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
To make mistakes. And so this sort of applies to you and to me and to participants. You know, so, you know, if you've got a scarcity of time, maybe you're trying, you're rushing, maybe you make a mistake.
153 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
You know, maybe, you know, if you're, you know, when your bandwidth is taxed, you can't spend the adequate time with somebody and you start making mistakes. And this tends to be.
154 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Something that tends to happen when our bandwidth is taxed like that, is we start only focusing on the most urgent thing or the thing that's right in front of us that we have to do. And so that is an idea called tunneling.
155 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Or to tony. And so they focus people focus on the most immediate need. So people walk in on what's urgent right in front of them and everything else sort of fades out. That includes kind of longer term thinking, weighing trade offs between different.
156 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Things, they all get pushed aside. There's a really kind of horrifying but also amazing study that sort of emphasizes this and it's called the Minnesota Starvation experiment. And it's, it's very famous. It took place in the 1940s.
157 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
1944. And 36 men volunteered. They were conscientious objectives to the war, so they they they needed to do some kind of service, but they weren't gonna go bite. And they volunteered to be starved for six months, basically have their calorie intake cut in half. And the reason why they were doing this.
158 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Was not to torture these four men, but to with the understanding that with the war coming to an end like they people saw the war was gonna end, there was gonna be mass hunger across Europe and Asia. And the point of the study was to see what happens to people when they've been starved and how you can maybe help them to like move past that to to help them after this happens. So anyway, so back to these men. They lost tons of weight, but in addition to that.
159 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Physical effect of having these calories reduced. There was also psychological effects. The men became obsessed with food. They would read and read cookbooks, they'd like stare into restaurant windows, and when they would watch movies, they would like ignore the plot conversations in the movies and just like.
160 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Only pay attention when food was on the screen. This is like a very extreme version of tunnel, right? They, their immediate need, what they wanted most was to eat something and so everything else sort of faded into the background.
161 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
I think one kind of important point about these men that is kind of useful for thinking of other people who are experiencing scarcity is that these people were not like weak willed, you know? They volunteered.
162 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Too starved. They were not, they were, that's very, I mean, they were brave, right? And even knowing that, even knowing what was gonna be involved, their cognition changed, how they thought changed. So tunneling experience happens at all.
163 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Levels of scarcity. So if you're, you know, if you're have limited income and your rents coming up, you're gonna focus on your rent, even if you've got, you know, a hospital bill coming next, right? It, it affects that ability to do that. If if if I, you know, yesterday I have a lot of things to do on my plate, but I was doing this today. So I focused on this, right? I had like a little bit of time and I wanted to make sure I could do my presentation.
164 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
You know, as well as like maybe do it. So when people are tunneling, they can't access all of the different things that they may need to really be also thinking about.
165 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
So, now let's move on to thinking about poverty as it is how poverty and scarcity.
166 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Work together in particular ways. So I'm gonna tell you a story that I heard on MPR like long, long time ago, that was all about behavioral science and scarcity. And it's about this, this woman named Brandy.
167 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And this is, this is part of her story. So, she was in a rush. She says, I was just in a rush to get home because daycare closes at six. I get off at five, it's like a 10 mi drive at busy traffic, and I had to pick up diapers before picking up her kid.
168 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And, you know, she was very tunneling tunneled on picking up diapers, right? And trying to get everything done. And this is an example of scarcity of time, right?
169 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And so she ended up making a mistake. She used the wrong card to pay for her diapers. She used her business card and it ended up with her losing her job that she had ten years. And after that.
170 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
You know, so that one small mistake had led to this big, big problem. And after that, you know, she still needed things for the house and she had a credit card that she maxed out 500 bucks on household supplies. And by the time she paid it off, she owed, you know, over $800 with all, with all the interest and stuff.
171 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And so there's, there's tunneling at two levels here. 1st of all, there was tunneling given the time that led to this mistake. And then there's tunneling on the financial side, which it wasn't exactly a mistake, but maybe she wasn't considering or wasn't able to consider sort of the medium term.
172 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Repercussions of maxing up the credit card and her ability to repay it she didn't do that because she couldn't do math, you know, or didn't understand, but like she had needs that needed to be fulfilled that day.
173 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
So this story I think is very useful for understanding scarcity and poverty for several reasons. One, we see several different types of scarcity here, scarcity of time, and scarcity of finances, and also I think what we see.
174 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Is that for somebody who's living kind of close to the edge financially, a small mistake has a much bigger repercussion than it might have for folks who have either less tenuous jobs.
175 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Or just a larger income to fall back on, you know? If she had had savings, you know, maybe she wouldn't have needed to more savings, she might needed to max out the credit card, things like that. So researchers were kind of interested in exploring like kind of more specifically what.
176 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Happens to people when they have scarcity on their mind. And so they they ran an experiment. So the researchers, they were from Princeton and Harvard, they went to a mall in New Jersey and they stopped sharp shoppers.
177 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And they spread presented one of two scenarios to them and then they gave them a cogni cognition test. It's called the progressive Raven test. I should include a photo, a picture of it because it's like it's not an it's not a knowledge test, it's a like how's your Can your brain.
178 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Makes sense of these images sort of test. So here's the 1st scenario. Imagine you've got car trouble and repairs costs $300. Your auto insurance will cover half the cost. You need to decide whether to go ahead and get the car fixed or take a chance and hope that it lasts a little while longer.
179 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
How would you make the decision financially, would it be easier or hard? So they presented this, they got answers from the patrons, and then they did the cognition test. I'll just ask you briefly, if you think they then compared kind of the results of the cognition test between folks who have said.
180 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
That who reported having lower incomes and higher incomes. Now enter in the chat, do you think that there was that the lower income people performed better than the higher income people Worse than the higher income people or are they performed exactly the same?
181 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Seeing comments going in different directions. Worse, better, better, yeah. I've seen a bunch of different explanations for this and let me know if this rings true. Folks say worse.
182 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Because they are already having often that they say that, you know, they're already stressed out, this would, this would affect it. Other people say NO low income people actually are used to these kinds of situations and their brains are sort of trained to make these sort of payoffs and they'll perform better. In fact, in this experiment, they've performed actually exactly the same. They're cognitive.
183 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Performance between lower income and higher income people was the same. There was NO statistical, there's NO difference between So I think I said they did two definitely depends, by the way. So they had two versions of this scenario.
184 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
One was like this and the other was like this. I'm sure you all saw that differ, so it was the same structure that you know now though the cost of the car repairs.
185 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Were $3000 and then they performed the same cognitive test. Now I wanna instead of doing the chat, I want us to go to a poll. Again, let's go back to the poll.
186 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And, I think if you have it on your phone, I think I'll just skip to the next one here. And I want you to think how does this change your answer for the $3000? Do you think it's the same that low income and high and and high had the same results? Low income people had more score.
187 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Or high income people had more scores. I'll let therapy a bunch of responses.
188 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Well, seeing things change in real time. Yeah, it's fun, right?
189 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
U.
190 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Alright, so it looks like every a lot of people think that low income people had worse scores when, when they changed the scenario from $300.
191 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
To $3000. Some people said few a handful of people said same results, and some people said high income people had worse course. Thank you. So.
192 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Remember before when it was $300 they had the same results. So I'm now gonna give you the roofy. So there was an IQ drop for folks with lower incomes when we made it moved it from $300.
193 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
To $3000. It was a 14 point IQ drop based on this intelligence test, which I don't understand IQ points and what they mean, but the researchers do.
194 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And this is the, the same difference that you might see if somebody was labeled superior to average intelligence, but I think what the thing is that people that is kind of more understandable to me is that you see this IQ same kind of level of IQ drop.
195 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
For people who remained to stay awake for 24 h. So if you imagine yourself having them like if you've had like had to stay awake for that long, how smart you feel at the end of being awake, 1420 4 h versus at the beginning Well not maybe not the beginning, say it after you've had your cup of coffee or tea or whatever, that.
196 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Is huge. I feel very dumb at the end of the day compared to, maybe right now I feel relatively intelligent right now. So it's a huge huge change. Now I'll note that like people have tried to replicate this study and they haven't always found this 14 point.
197 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Change it varies, which makes sense because you're seeing different people, you're doing slightly different things, but still directionally, like it still points in the same direction that by kind of getting people to think about a higher cost of something, it affects.
198 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Their cognition. Now, I think that a subtle point about that experiment is that they weren't, they, the researchers weren't going out there with baseball bats and smashing people's cars.
199 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Right? They weren't actually faced with this huge financial stressor. They were just told to think about just imagine it, and that resulted in this, this drop in cognition. So, you know, imagine what this might be like then.
200 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
For folks who are really living in this constantly, kind of distant but sort of related thing is, was about farmers in India, and they did the same kind of test. In fact, I think it's the same researchers, did the same test to sugarcame farmers before and after the harmest.
201 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And the same sort of thing happened. Cognitive performance approved after they were paid, not because they changed, but because scarcity had lifted. One other point I want to make about that previous example about between the lower income and higher income people is that the underlying intelligence scores were the same. Remember like at the beginning, when it was $300, they got the same.
202 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Pain results. It was only one that financial burden kind of increased that you saw a divergence. I think that's like kind of a very crucial point. It's not about sort of underlying ability, but it's about the stressors.
203 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And making a scarcity feel real that changes cognition. And one thing that I think is important related to the sugar sugar farm or sugar cane example is that for those who are in persistent property, there is NO parts, right?
204 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
There I mean there might be like a monthly check, but like, it's not, it's not gonna be as big of a windfall, and there's NO cushion. And things that might be trivial mistakes for those of us who have even slightly higher incomes can be very catastrophic as we saw from Brandy's example.
205 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
So a lot of what I've been talking about, as I mentioned before, comes from a field called behavioral science. Sometimes it's called behavioral economics, depending on who you want to give credit for. And it's been building for the past, 40 years.
206 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
It's actually kind of comes from several different fields, including psychology, you know, how people are thinking, economics, which I think a lot of the would say is about how people make decisions, marketing, what, how context kind of face it, affects people's choices, and also neuroscience, what actually is kind of going on inside of people's brains.
207 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And people have, applied this to a variety of different, sectors, everything from retirement savings enrollment, to organ donation. I used to work when I worked in the federal government, I worked in a briefly in an office called the Office of Evaluation Science. A lot.
208 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Their work was all about kind of behavioral science and kind of making small tweaks to programs to improve them in different ways. There have been a lot of interesting findings from, from this. One is that shorter deadlines actually tend to produce greater responsiveness than longer deadlines. You know, a longer deadline feels less actionable and less so people are less likely to start.
209 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Are doing stuff on it, I think, I mean, I I was a teenager who definitely waited till the night before test study, so I sort of understand that inclination. And also that too many choices can lead to NO choice at all. That if you have too many things, it feels like too work, too much work to decide, and so sometimes.
210 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Sometimes shortening the list of choices can increase uptake. So the core kind of question that behavioral science tries to answer is why, why don't people behave rationally a lot of the time? So it starts with the assumption that people are humans, not like.
211 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Rational calculator robots, that we have a lot of stuff going on, feelings, life, that means that we don't always make what's considered the most rational decision. And it's trying to understand what actually, what affects our decisions, what drives our behavior. A lot of programs.
212 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Are built with the assumption that people behave rationally. And so behavioral science can actually help us learn a lot about, what, why people may not behave in the ways we think within terms. So I want to give like an example, it's a bit of a an example of how.
213 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
How people actually make decisions. So there's sort of like the traditional view of rational decision making, which is like you weigh on the left side, you weigh the available information that exists, you assess the costs and benefits of the choice you're trying to make, and then you make the best.
214 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Personal choice and then you take that action. The behavioral view is a bit more like, like my life, which is I'm like, oh, I've got to sign up for insurance. Where did I put the email that said had my stuff that had that and then I have to like search and find it and I like read the email, but I don't understand what it's saying.
215 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And then I'm confused about when I'll have to pay for it, so I need to figure out when my paycheck is, but I'm not even sure if I'll ever really need this insurance anyway, like maybe I should actually kind of risk it and then by actually kind of feel like I need to decide and I guess I'll pick this one, but it's annoying to sign up because I have to fill up all this paperwork, so I'm just gonna do it tomorrow. That's close.
216 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Sort of how I live my life than like the 1st thing, I don't know about you if any of you can actually go through like a rational decision process like I've laid out on the left and I'm like, I think I I think we should like you should actually do a different session and tell us how you live your life in such an efficient way.
217 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Cause I'd be interested in that. So I think the thing is, is that basically life kind of in the best of days life gets in the way of rational decision making. It it's not that.
218 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Behavioral, this behavioral mall, it isn't a failing. It's just like an honest description of how we live our lives under real and conditions that like just life gets in the way. But our systems exacerbate behavioral barriers for ourselves, for workers, and.
219 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
For participants, you know, the forms, the processes, timelines, the volume of information, it often kind of makes it, makes rational decision making harder and you know, they're the systems are designed for this traditional model of behavi of rational decision.
220 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
They assume a rational actor with time, information, and low stress. They may not even have mentioned those assumptions, but they're kind of baked in. And that is not most people, and not certainly not most people most of the time, and it's certainly not somebody who's experiencing scarcity. They are definitely not a person who is in a space to make purely rational decisions.
221 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
So one way to best understand this kind of concept of, kind of behavioral barriers, there are a lot of different behavioral barriers that have been identified over time, but one of the best ones is one called hassle factor or hassle.
222 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Hassle factors. So hassle factor is anything that creates friction between a person and the action that they need to take, even when they fully intend to take that action.
223 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
So you probably recognize, sorry, here's that 1st bullet. You probably recognize the background here as like the old, maybe I don't know how often people actually fill out the paper form anymore, with, oh my god, how am I forgetting the nate with the the be the benefits thing? Anyway.
224 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And then benefits, that's that right? Moving for a non. Thank you. Okay, anyway, this, this is a great example of a hassle factor. So, you know, that this, you know, we might intend to mail a document for weeks.
225 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
But then like finding that stamp to actually like put it on can be that one hassle that makes us delay sending something a day. You know, this, the, the, the calf is like a really.
226 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Amazing example of a hassle factor. And actually, and then benefits is an example of how, how we at the state have tried to overcome a hassle factor and maybe created different kinds of scarcity for other people, but we could maybe talk about that later.
227 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
So, you know, this, the cath, it starts, you know, with two pages of like dense language that I think, you know, I do believe people have tried to make, you know, I'm forgetting the term, but like very readable, I don't believe that, but still.
228 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
If you're not familiar with things, you know, it can be confusing, you know, what, this is old, like what if the diversionary work program is now plain language, thank you Steph. You know, I do believe we've tried to make this plain language, but still it's like a lot of words to like start off from the back, from the start. There is jargon, you know, if you're.
229 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Not familiar with things like supplemental nutrition assistance program feels like a lot, like snap. What is like if I didn't know that Snap meant food support or food, like I would be like looking for food stamps all over here. You know, that is kind of the more traditional like still people think in that terms.
230 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
You know, there's a lot of stuff on here. So thinking about like somebody who's come into the program for like 1st time, especially if they've like just worked a lot. They are have a low, they have they're hungry. All of this is gonna feel like a big barrier to even make.
231 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Taking that 1st step, you know, let alone like if there's another kind of barrier like maybe some of we can't read well, sorry, oh, Eileen, do you wanna just say what you just said?
232 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Sure. Well, I just have had the most experience with the childcare application being denied. There's an awful lot of required documents and it's a long application, and then there's often kind of a missing communication loop where people will say I had NO idea that they needed the daycare or the birth certificate and.
233 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
It's a pretty short window to hold it open. And then, you know, the scanning center can be delayed too, and they can't, maybe they can't get in touch with their workers so I just feel like I've had a lot of people being denied and having NO idea that they needed something else. So I just thought statistically it would be interesting to, to learn how.
234 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
How many applications are turned in perfectly the 1st go? And then if they are denied, what percentage of, let's say there are there are seven required documents or something? Like what percentage is missing? Is it like just one or is it everything? I don't know, just stats?
235 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Yeah, I think that would be really, really interesting. And if you found like if it was one particular form, you know, that could be one lesson. If it's everything, that's like a different type of lesson. That's what, you know, I love researching things so like you just like tickle my fancy as they say.
236 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
So I, I would also say that this also affects like it goes both ways, you know, as a worker, like, like you have to also track all of those things and figure out which of those things that somebody needs. Like that's also a hassle for you that you don't know as somebody's trying to help somebody get.
237 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Support which of those things it is. So maybe, you know, some people might or might not be willing or feel like they're able to go through that process to figure it out. So there's also the kind of structure of this is an example, but there's a structure to this.
238 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
That is similar and affects also workers. Alright, you Eileen actually like teed me off for the next slide, which I appreciate, and this, this can be group for all of us, but i'd love to see.
239 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
People share examples of hassle factors in your work, you know, maybe if I'm not sure if we want every, if, if you have something to speak say go for it, maybe just like raise your hand so Eileen can like manage that flow, but you can also enter it into the chat, but I'd love to spend a few minutes hearing what people.
240 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Hassle factors people think they experienced him work in their work.
241 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Go Steph.
242 "Steph Randby - DWD" (1855006976)
Okay, I'm not sure if my sound is working, if my sound is.
243 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Working yes it is. Okay.
244 "Steph Randby - DWD" (1855006976)
Awesome. All right, I think a big hassle factor that I think of mainly for participants is the fact that everything that comes from our county eligibility office is through snail mail. So by the time something is due for verifications, their case might already be off. And so I think that's something that we're always working with and always having to work around with participants, and I think that that is one of the biggest hassle factors that our our folks deal with all.
245 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Time. Do they have to also submit their stuff by paper or in person?
246 "Steph Randby - DWD" (1855006976)
Yeah. They can turn it in through, like they can take photos of the application and turn it into an email or to our portal now, which is supreme, that's so much more beneficial and now the part our county can put like the CAF, e.g., into the portal so our participants can access that, but that just changed just recently. So I'm hoping that that will help some of the the leg time, but I feel like that's a big bear.
247 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Yeah, but I I like that you like you've also shown examples of things that were hassle factors and approach it and clear approaches to try to address them which is also really useful and I'm sure like how would you, do you have any thought of how you would address the stale mail hassle factor?
248 "Steph Randby - DWD" (1855006976)
You know, I think this, you know, it's something that the county eligibility offices it comes above them, right? It's it's a state requirement or something that these documents have to go out through the mail, so I'm not sure where the change has to come.
249 "Steph Randby - DWD" (1855006976)
If It's of change or if it is, it's not quite that high, I'm not sure but I think the, you know, one way that I try to help mitigate it is if I see that something is due for a participant I'm trying to maybe interrupt that process and provide that document to them, you know, through edocs where I can print it out myself for them. Yeah. Awesome.
250 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Thanks Steph. Would anybody else like to speak and share?
251 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And if not Eileen, do you have anything that you're seeing in the chat that you.
252 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
There's a lot. Something that got a lot of reactions is animal's comment of more case management than actual career coaching. Oh yeah. And I think that that has especially if you're doing extension cases especially if you're doing FSS cases where people may have additional barriers, we're not getting the, you know, the popular perception of everyone's ready to work. It's like NO there's a lot of stabilization that needs to happen.
253 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Interesting. I was thinking about, ok, so I was thinking about that actually a different way. So you said case management versus career coaching. Yeah so ok I think one way I had thought about it when you 1st said it as like because.
254 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Is there's like a lot of kind of bureaucratic processes that you have to take care of, and so like that would mean like you have a limited time, so you have to tunnel on those bureaucratic steps rather than support people with career oriented coaching. So that's how that's how I 1st thought of it, but you were saying that there's like, because there's different kinds of client clients, is that right?
255 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Annabelle, do you maybe wanna explain the nuance of your comment because it could definitely be taken more than one way.
256 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Oh, the 1st freak. Okay, which which was sorry which was the 1st one, was that about the what what Eileen said? Oh, you think so. Okay, good, good. Ok I'm just trying to think.
257 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
No me! Yes. Go me. Yeah, ok, yeah, I definitely see that as like, definitely a hassle factor. I'm also now just like trying to think of like what the behavioral scientists would say about like, about doing.
258 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
About switching between like FSS type support and career support. But certainly like those bureaucratic steps that must be, that's a like a great example of a hassle factor. I think that most people probably.
259 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Didn't, like, aren't motivated to do this work because they're very passionate about filling out forms but like are like interested in helping people. Like, I mean, I I believe it or not, I I I am a person who loves math, but loves to do math to try to help.
260 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And so that's like what my motivation is. Oh cool hi cool. Good to see you, by the way, that's great. Anything, anything else that people, any other kind of themes you're seeing Eileen?
261 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
It looks like there's a lot of factors, you know, work life balance, high caseloads is something that we hear a lot. It's really hard to, you know, do everything you need to for one case both with the, you know, relationship piece and the paperwork piece if you have 87 other participants waiting for your service.
262 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Yeah, can I just put a pin in? I would love that if we could try to save hopefully, maybe we can try to save the chat and maybe if we know who came to this we could try to like summarize it because I think these would be really useful for us to to remember how how similar we are and maybe like make help make a list of like what should what should we be attacking to try to help.
263 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Ourselves and others. Alright, thank you guys so much. I'm gonna move on. So, and we'll have more discussion later. So now like we have an example where of what scare City does and how our systems sort of make it worse.
264 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
He we kind of want to know what we can do about it and I think we've already heard a few things and I think we can fit them into a few of these ideas. Here are three sort of principles, they're not like this is what you do, but kind of ideas that can motivate directions of change. So the 1st is about cutting costs. So this is not about budget.
265 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
That I'm not saying like, oh, you know what it really help is if we everybody had less money. I'm not saying that. What I'm saying is like by cutting costs I mean like costs that are about frictions and costs that are about creating, reducing inconvenience. So cutting costs reduces friction that can create that the pleaps bandwidth. So that's what costs cut cost cutting costs. Second thing is creating slack.
266 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And creating Slack reduces now the, the consequences of tunneling, right? Okay, so if you are tunneling on something and make a mistake, if you're low income that tends to have much worse.
267 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Repercussions. So if we have slack, then maybe that the repercussions won't be so disastrous. And the last thing reframing and empowering changes kind of the dynamics of the interaction and treats families as experts.
268 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Alright, so we're gonna look at in each of these in a little bit more depth right now. So the 1st one cutting costs, I have an example, and I think we've also talked about a few different examples already.
269 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
But this one is from, a Michigan works, which was a program in Michigan, obviously, that would be weird if it was in South Koreta or something, but let's say it's in Michigan, that was designed to help people on UI return to work, but uptake was very low.
270 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And before assuming that just like the program itself didn't work, the researchers wanted to ask what is there a friction present preventing people from engaging with this program? And so what the intervention was, was they designed email.
271 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Emails that were addressed personally, instead of dear recipient, you know dear Cassie, the instructions were short and concrete. They weren't like buried within paragraphs. There were also reminders that arrived.
272 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
There were planning prompts to help people figure out what they needed to do the next step. So all of these things are like behaviorally, behavioral insights that, that researchers have learned, help people to overcome different kinds of behavioral barriers.
273 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And the researcher has like randomly selected different potential participants into a group that received this redesign form versus those who did not. They didn't.
274 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Redesign the whole program, right? They just changed how people accessed the program program, right? How they communicated. And it worked. Those who were randomized to receive these misundated encouragement were more likely to set up a session and to.
275 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Complete the program. I'll say they weren't like enormous effects. It wasn't like 5 % to a hundred percent. It was like 5 % to 10 %, but that's kind of the nature of these behavioral changes. They are small, and so our expectation of how much they affect things should also be small.
276 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
But I do think it is really important that they didn't change anything about the program, right? They did not do that. They just removed reduced the friction, and that improved access and improved.
277 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Completion. So if cutting costs again is about reducing frictions so that bandwidth is not taxed. 2nd principle of creating Slack is about building room for when things don't.
278 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Go the same go go right. Okay, so I like when I think of creating slack, I like to use a car example cause I I have a lot of car thoughts about packing cars. I love, I kind of love packing cars honestly, and I'll tell you what. So if you've got like.
279 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Like a large car, which I have three sons, so we have a mini van, but previously we had a smaller car, and let me tell you, mini van is freaking beat because I can just throw stuff in there and there is room. In fact, we went on a road trip over spring break and you know they all wanted to bring stuffies, and I was like, go for it. You can bring a stufffy, that is NO problem because I could just put it in the car and it was easy, and if, you know, we had gotten to ready to go and my five year old said.
280 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
I forgot Luna, that's his stuff, dog, NO problem. I can just grab Luna and put her in. But if we had a small car and they said we forgot something, that would mean repacking the entire car, right? Cause.
281 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
When you have a small car, right, you have to put everything in exactly the right spot to get everything in there. I was in a band when I was 19 and, we did like we actually toward the country in a civic hatchback to your car.
282 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
That a drum set in there, guitarian, three people. We had to like pack the people in and if I didn't put everything in exactly the right order, you would not fit everything in the car. So that was not, right? That was repacking completely if I forgot everything.
283 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
So, if you now apply this to money, there's a big, big difference between living with financial slack and living without. For someone with savings.
284 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Or someone who just has an overall higher income, an unexpected car repair, an increased medical bill, that's annoying, but it doesn't mean your life has to be completely reshaped, right? If you don't have a cushion.
285 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
That can lead to a cascade, you know, getting the car repaired maybe means that being late on your rent, which might mean a fee, which might mean being late on an electric bill. You know, all these things can cascade when you don't have slack, especially in finances.
286 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And when we apply this to programs, you know, as we were talking about before, missing something can trigger, can, can, you know, create a lot of problems. So like a missed deadline can end up not opening benefits or having benefits be closed, you know.
287 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And a document not being submitted, maybe again means that you, you don't get to have the benefits or the cases closed or the the yeah. So if we can look for opportunities where we can create slack or a grace period or an automatic reminder, exactly. That's a great example Dina.
288 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
That is the cascade. So if we in our programs can create slack or opportunities that help people, you know, cut those costs that can improve their experience and and help them better.
289 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
So we should be always looking for opportunities that create slack in time, in resources, and in processes. Now, I'm just looking through my next couple of slides because we're gonna have a couple more channels.
290 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Is to, to ask them. So thinking back on the costs and now this, I want you 1st to share any places where you feel like are, oh, there we go, sorry, where.
291 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
What costs our systems put on you? I think we sort of started kind of talking about it, but if you want to share some places where you think the systems or how we run our program put costs on you as a, as a person who works within the system.
292 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And I'd like to try to keep that focused on you rather than participants. Again, feel free to talk or chat.
293 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
So that's sort of Annabelle, that's I see that as like other people to help, like less resources within a place. Testa, that's a really interesting one.
294 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
I think that they those are really, those last couple about mental health is really interesting because it's, it can be stressful working with some participants. It's a great example. You're like Billbo.
295 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Oh, interesting, Tony.
296 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
It drives me a little nuts, and that happens so many places. Yep, I agree, and Eileen, it's a good point. Yeah.
297 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Yeah, that's a great example of Teresa.
298 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Yeah.
299 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Yep, concept policy changes.
300 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Yeah, that is a cost, isn't it? Because it's not like.
301 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
They're obvious. There are also, I do think that last point, like where we are in the state, there's gonna be different levels of resources within our counties, within our communities that can support people.
302 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Staff turnover, that's another good example Eileen because you have to train somebody up. I always feel like it takes like me like nine months to know what I'm doing in my job when I change jobs like at the best. At the same time I'll say new people also bring new ideas, which I think is.
303 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Alright, thank you very much. Let's keep chatting and again feel free to actually speak but also totally happy with chat as well. Where do you think, do you think that there were opportunities to create more slack? And what, what might they be?
304 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Yeah. It's.
305 "Juliana Martignacco Hired, NL" (162036992)
That's something to ask question and this question.
306 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Yeah. I'm with North Loop.
307 "Juliana Martignacco Hired, NL" (162036992)
M FIP extension. I was just gonna say that one thing that I feel is a a cost or a lack or is just when participants aren't motivated or have big barriers that make it difficult for them to have the hope of moving forward or see the light at the end of the tunnel that they can achieve more than they thought they could.
308 "Juliana Martignacco Hired, NL" (162036992)
And for a lot of my participants, that's mental health and and disabilities that, that make it a struggle. It it costs a little bit of our hope sometimes, and I'm not always discouraged I'm a very positive, hopeful person, and I've overcome so much so I know my participants can, you know, benefit from that.
309 "Juliana Martignacco Hired, NL" (162036992)
Hope and so I keep it strong, but at times, you know, it can be a little bit discouraging to hear them on the other end of the phone, you know, that they, well, just even having that empathy and compassion because I have so strong for them because I've been there. I was a single mom, I was on MFIP and so the struggle is very, very real. But I would say here with Slack, what I like to do with my participants is sometimes help them feel like.
310 "Juliana Martignacco Hired, NL" (162036992)
About an application, you know, like mine wanted to go to the medical office administration career pathways program, so I helped them fill out the career pathways application because they struggled to do so on their device. And I think just taking those extra 5 min, creating that slack so that we can really do.
311 "Juliana Martignacco Hired, NL" (162036992)
You know, assist them in a way that's tangible and makes it possible for them to move ahead and and she smiled really big with all her teeth in an emoji afterwards. So that was fun.
312 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
I love that. Thank you for your work. Thank you. You actually like made me feel like turning to the next thing, which is, you know, we've talked a lot about I've tried to talk a little bit about participants but also about you as workers. And I'd like if people can reflect and feel comfortable sharing how their own feelings of scarcity.
313 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Affect your work with participants. You know, when you're in the middle of something high volume, you're stressed, like how does that affect how you work with people? You know, I mean I, I I I as I said I'm a dad of three little kids and sometimes I get stressed and not every day am I the best dad that I won't be?
314 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And that's part of, part of, part of life. But I'd be curious to know how you see it, how you see your own scarcity affect those interactions.
315 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Dina.
316 "Deena Schlueter" (4229673472)
I apologize in advance there's some construction outside my window so if there's any background noise, but I think in two different ways I have experienced the financial scarcity, so understanding some of that fear and maybe not always making the best decisions when you're experiencing that.
317 "Deena Schlueter" (4229673472)
So I can relate on the one hand to clients or if some of those hassle factors interfere, you know, with getting items in, I completely relate to and empathize with that. Yeah. And then on the other hand, scarcity of my own time off or my own like self care, I can see when I maybe I'm starting to feel impatient or have, have less grace.
318 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Give your city is impacting me in that way. Yeah, it's real. It's real that we we should be we're all, we're all human all the time. That's my wife likes to say and.
319 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
It can affect everything we do and I think being aware of that is the the at the very least we should we need to accept it. All right. Thank you. So.
320 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
The last kind of principle I mentioned was about reframing and empowering, and actually I wanted to come back to Juliana and your comment back some people not having hope and how that's that's hard. I don't know why.
321 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
There we go. Sorry, it didn't I moved it forward it didn't show up. So a while ago, anyway, Juliana, your point, like, a while ago I was at this conference and there was a participant former participant panel as part of the conference and.
322 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
This young woman was talking about kind of what she had had like grown up, like, always on public assistance, and she they they asked her kind of how how did she kind of.
323 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Managed to like get out of that cycle that her family had been on. And she said that she had a counselor that asked her what she wanted from her. And, you know, maybe other counselors should ask this for this before, maybe.
324 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
I I like to think she was in the right frame of mind to hear that question because it seems like a question that a lot of people would ask and she heard it and that's what really spurred her to make, to make changes in how she was living and creative plans and great goals.
325 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
That got her off the the cycle, and she felt listened to. I think it's a really like good example of reframing and empowering people and it gets and here's there are a few examples of of what in framing empowering could look like. You know, intentional language is something that i've tried to do here and we've also sort of kind of.
326 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Throughout our conversation. You know, I've I don't say four people, I say people with low incomes. Try to say participant not case. You know, there was this discussion about like case management versus being a coach, you know, those sorts of those terms maybe can make a difference in how people are perceived and how people can work together.
327 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Another interesting thing is plausible paths. So, you know, presenting examples of people who have been in similar situations and how people have made paths to, you know.
328 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Hire incomes or other things that can be very useful and they can also kind of lead to concrete plans of action that have, you know, shorter time frames that allow people to sort of move forward. Second next is kind of treating families as experts that they know their lives better than.
329 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Any of us could and help making decisions with them and also understanding community and relations that, you know, sometimes emphasizing social connection and collective can success can be a better kind of messaging for some people than individuals.
330 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Self sufficiency. You know, so maybe an example is like, who supports you might be something and rather than what's Your you were gonna say we're almost at the end, aren't it?
331 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Yeah, there's time for you to, for you.
332 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Okay, I have to I'm trying to decide if, ok, I'm gonna skip this next one.
333 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
About how you plan to reframe and instead, I want you to try to think, I would love to hear if there's based on what we've said, if there's one thing you think you might try to do differently next week. This is always a hard question and I kind of hate though when I'm asked them, but I want to give it a try. I've never asked this.
334 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Question before. Is there anything that you all might try to do differently, either with participants, within your organizations next week in the context of what we've talked about today?
335 "Juliana Martignacco Hired, NL" (162036992)
This is Juliana again and I just wanted to say I would like to ask my participants, what do you want in life? So that's what I'm gonna start trying next week and moving forward.
336 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
That's great. Thanks Juliana.
337 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Of that, of powerful questions.
338 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Feel free to keep adding them, but I'm going to.
339 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Go to I only have one more slide, so I'm gonna go through it and it's a conclusion slide, so this is a easy one, but, at the beginning I started by asking you what a financial worker, a mom, with bills and a food insecure person having called us.
340 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
And the answer was scarcity. As we've seen it today, it's not scarcy affects everybody. It's not a character flow, ok? It's a condition that affects our cognition, it narrows our focus and makes it more likely that we make mistakes.
341 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
It's not something, some bad thing about ourselves, something that happens to us. Our systems create barriers for both our workers and participants.
342 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
That, that affect our ability to make good decisions even in the best of times. And when.
343 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Our worker, who's tunneling meeting meets participant, who's tunneling, this is like a collision. But it's also where an opportunity lips because if you understand what's happening in that moment.
344 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
We can design things differently, we can communicate differently, and we can respond different, and that can make bigger change. The three principles of cutting costs, creating slack, reframing and impairing, can make our programs and our interactions.
345 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
None of these things necessarily require a new program or a new policy. Obviously that stuff can help. But you know, all of this can start with like you guys have mentioned, y'all have mentioned, a different question in the next conversation.
346 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
It starts with removing one step, one unnecessary step. It starts by adding a little more grace that costs a very little bit. And you know, these small changes apply constantly consistently as much as we can.
347 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Can compound and help folks reach their successes. Thank you all so much for a great conversation. It was great to be here and feel free to be in touch.
348 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
With me, so I don't know if that phone number's real. But anyway, feel free to email me, if you want. I love doing this session, so if you want me to come to your agency and do it again, I'd be happy to, just send me a note. And it's great to see people. I haven't seen in a long time even if they are just text boxes.
349 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
So, thank you all very much. I hope you have a great rest of the conference.
350 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Thank you so much, Ben. This was really informative. I hope people will be in touch to learn more. Cole, did you oh NO, ok. So yeah, please, please use the survey link to fill out the survey. We really value your feedback.
351 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
The session was recorded, so if you missed something and wanted to go back, and then the Ben's presentation materials will be sent out as well. Thank you guys again. See you at 1040 for the next breakout session. Maybe it will be with me, maybe it won't. Have a great rest of your day. Bye everyone.
352 "MMB CLOUD R CEDAR COB/speaker_1" (146916864_1)
Bye.
353 "Eileen Lewis" (1172762368)
Oh, thanks steph. Yeah, I believe the survey link will be sent out as well too, so if you didn't get a chance to grab it, there will be, will be sent out right Jonathan?
354 "Jonathan P. Hausman" (1387315968)
That's right, it's on partner link for all the, all the sessions. Fabulous.